http://www.plasmatech.co.uk/privacy-policy

My Account
Register
Login
Wish List (0)
COMPETITIVE PRICING
Substantial cost savings from OEM pricesPrices shown exclude VAT
DELIVERY SCHEDULE
Order dispatched within one working day**subject to availability
FREE UK DELIVERY
Free delivery on all goods except liquids
Privacy Policy
Categories
Plasma Consumables & Spares (142)
Ajan (5)
American Torch Tip (14)
Cebora (3)
Hypertherm (49)
Kaliburn (63)
SAF (3)
Thermal Dynamics (5)
Plasma Cutting Accessories (12)
Plasma Water Treatment (2)
Plasma O-Ring Lubricant (1)
Plasma Torch Coolant (1)
Plasma Anti spatter (1)
Plasma Filters (2)
Omniport CNC Adaptors (1)
Torch Height Control (1)
Plasma torch anti-collision (1)
Gasfluxer & Gasflux (13)
Gasflux (1)
Gasfluxers (3)
Spares (8)
Plasmalighter (1)
Eye Protection (6)
Aluminium Welding & Gasflux Brazing (2)
Plasma Cutting (4)
Business privacy policy
This privacy policy sets out how Plasmatech OnLine Limited uses and protects any information that you give Plasmatech OnLine Limited when you use this Website under the Data Protection Act 1998 and the General Data Protection Regulations
Plasmatech OnLine Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Plasmatech OnLine Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page in order to make sure it stays up to date with the latest legal requirements, and make changes to our privacy management practices. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes to this policy. This policy is effective from This policy is effective from May 24th 2018.
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address and telephone number
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer enquiries, surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide our services, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
You can learn more about Cookies including how to manage and delete Cookies from your computer at www.cookiesandyou.com as well as comprehensive information about a wide variety of browsers
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@plasmatech.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
For the purpose of the DPA and GDPR we are the data controller. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 and General Data Protection Regulations. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Plasmatech OnLine Ltd, PO Box 3667, Stafford ST16 9TN
You have the right to change the permissions that you have given us in relation to how we may use your data. You also have the right to request that we cease using your data or that we delete all personal data records that we hold relating to you.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
How 'Plasmatech Online Ltd.' uses Cookies
Functional Cookies:
TS01237438 TS016d693e & BIGipServerZebedee : are set when you move from one page to another page in the site. The cookies are classed as "strictly necessary" for the functioning of the site, and as such they are exempt from the normal requirement of user consent for the use of cookies. Neither of these two cookies store personally identifiable information, and both of them (as "session cookies") are deleted when you close your browser session.
currency - used to define the currency in which product prices will be shown
language - used to define the language OpenCart will load
PHPSESSID - this holds the ID of the customer session
Google Universal Analytics:
_ga : This helps us count how many people visit our website by tracking if you’ve visited before
_gid : Used to distinguish users
_gat : Used to manage the rate at which page view requests are made
Google Maps:
Google set a number of cookies on any page that includes a Google Map. While we have no control over the cookies set by Google, they include a mixture of pieces of information to measure the number and behaviour of Google Maps users.
Social Networking:
Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons which allow visitors to share content onto social networks, or link to their business profile on the social network. Cookies are currently set on our site by Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and Google+. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing on the internet, including on the website you have linked from.
AddThis:
Cookies are set by AddThis which allows visitors to this website to add favourites and share content on Social Media.
Third Party Links:
Our website may have links to third party websites. These websites should have their own Cookie & Privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as these sites are out of our control.
Powered By OpenCart Plasmatech OnLine Ltd. © 2020Website built By Sunrise Web Studio
